A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, Pamphlet File, Series 2 FA264
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation records, Pamphlet File, Series 2
1878-1988
1935-1975
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation
FA264
23 Cubic Feet 41 manuscript boxes
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Scope and Contents
The Rockefeller Foundation Pamphlet Collection consists of 41 archival boxes and approximately 23 cu. ft. of records. The Rockefeller Foundation maintained a vast collection of published pamphlets, academic papers, book manuscripts, magazine articles, and other booklets that reference the Foundation or members of the Rockefeller family or were created by RF leaders, employees, or grantees. The pamphlets date from 1878 to 1988, with the majority containing dates between 1935 and 1975.
Arrangement
The collection is organized alphabetically by author, organization, or major subject, depending on the original classification by the Rockefeller Foundation.
Rockefeller Foundation
- Aa-Af, 1970-1982 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Ad Hoc Committee on the Huntington Estate Buildings, 1966 November (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Advertising Council, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Ag-Aj, 1957-1975 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Agency for International Development, 1970 January 7 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Ak-Ap, 1934-1973 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Aldrich, Nelson W., 1913 October 15 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Alfred E. Smith Memorial Exhibition, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Alroy, Gil Carl, 1966 June (Box 2, Folder 9)
- American Assembly, 1972 November 2-5 and 1975 April 3-5 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- American Assn. of Junior Colleges, 1941-1942 June (Box 2, Folder 11)
- American Association of State Libraries, 1963 July 13 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- American Cancer Society, 1969-1971 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- American Conservation Association, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- American School of Classical Studies at Athens, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- American Society of Agronomy, 1964 July and 1971 August 15-20 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- American Symphony Orchestra League, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- American Youth Commission, 1938 April (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Andrews, Wayne, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Angel, Herbert E., 1968 January (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Appleget, Thomas B., 1936 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Arbona, Guillermo, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Arnett, Trevor, 1937 and 1956 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Arnold, W. F., 1906 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Arnstein, Margaret G., 1956 July (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Art in Science, 1965 September (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Ashcraft, Virginia, 1947 November (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Atwater, Elton, 1936 May (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Atwood, J. Howell, 1941 May (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Australia Politics & Government, 1921 October 19-1923 August 25 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Bailey (Russell D.) and Associates, 1968 June (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Baird, Guy B., 1970 September 10-1971 March 15 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Barker, Randolph, 1970 March 2 - 1974 March 18 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Barnard, Chester I., 1939-1958 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Barnes, M.E., 1925 December 31 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Barreto, Pablo, 1970 September (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Barry, Iris, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Basch, Paul F., 1969 December (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Bates, Marston, 1952 January 10 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Batten, James K., 1962 June 30 (Box 3, Folder 40)
- Bauer, G. Philip, 1946 June (Box 3, Folder 41)
- Bavarian State Galleries, 1946 January 14 (Box 3, Folder 42)
- Beach, Fred F., 1949 (Box 3, Folder 43)
- Be-Bh, 1933-1982 (Box 3, Folder 44)
- Belkin, John N., 1965 (Box 4, Folder 45)
- Berger, Morroe, 1960 February 1 (Box 4, Folder 46)
- Bi-Bn, 1878 and 1984 (Box 4, Folder 47)
- Bly, Robert, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 48)
- Bo-Bt, 1938-1976 (Box 4, Folder 49)
- Boccaccio, Mary, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 50)
- Borlaug, Norman, 1965-1970 (Box 4, Folder 51)
- Organizing National Crop Production Campaigns by Norman Borlaug, 1968 April 2 (Box 4, Folder 52)
- Organizing National Crop Production Campaigns by Norman Borlaug, 1968 April 2 - June 27 (Box 4, Folder 53)
- Bowman, Isaiah, 1937 October (Box 4, Folder 54)
- Bu-Bz, 1955-1980; 1960-1975 (Box 5, Folder 55)
- British Columbia. Vancouver. Board of Parks and Recreation, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 56)
- Brookings Institution, 1931 and 1963 (Box 5, Folder 57)
- Brown, E. Richard, 1975-1980 (Box 5, Folder 58)
- Brumbaugh, A.J., 1942 January (Box 5, Folder 59)
- Brunner, Edmund deS., 1934 (Box 5, Folder 60)
- Health and the Developing World by John. H. Bryant, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 61)
- Health and the Developing World by John H. Bryant, 1968 May (Box 5, Folder 62)
- Buarque, de Holanda, Sergio, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 63)
- Buchanan, Norman S., 1944 (Box 5, Folder 64)
- Bull, Hedley, 1964 September 15 (Box 6, Folder 65)
- Bullock, Mary Brown, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 66)
- Bureau of Community Service, 1950-1951 (Box 6, Folder 67)
- Bureau of Public Administration (Tennessee), 1947 January - October (Box 6, Folder 68)
- Bureau of Public Schools, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 69)
- Burns, Arthur Lee, 1959 April 2 - June 8 (Box 6, Folder 70)
- Ca-Cd, 1958-1974 (Box 6, Folder 71)
- Cameron, John, 1929-1930 (Box 6, Folder 72)
- Campbell, Doak S., 1943 December (Box 6, Folder 73)
- Camps, Miriam, 1957-1960 (Box 7, Folder 74)
- Canadian Institute of International Affairs, 1935 (Box 7, Folder 75)
- Contril, Hadley, 1941 June (Box 7, Folder 76)
- Carter, Clarence E., 1952 May 22 (Box 7, Folder 77)
- Carter, Henry Rose, 1935-1941 (Box 7, Folder 78)
- Oral History Typescript. Causey, Otis R. and Calista, 1970 September 21-25 (Box 7, Folder 79)
- Ce-Ch, 1921-1975 (Box 7, Folder 80)
- A Celebration of..., 1979 (Box 7, Folder 81)
- Center for Inter-American Relations, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 82)
- Center for Southern Education Studies, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 83)
- Center of Planning and Economic Research, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 84)
- Central American Cooperative Corn Improvement Project, 1954-1956 (Box 7, Folder 85)
- Centro Internacional de Mejoramiento de Maiz y Trigo (CIMMYT), undated (1971-1972) (Box 7, Folder 86)
- Chamber of Commerce of the State of New York, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 87)
- Chamberlain, Weston P., 1929 (Box 8, Folder 88)
- Chambers, M. M., 1946 (Box 8, Folder 89)
- Chang, Te-Tzu, 1964 August-1965 December (Box 8, Folder 90)
- Chase, Stuart, 1946 (Box 8, Folder 91)
- Chavez, Ignacio, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 92)
- Ci-Cn, 1958-1977; 1958-1967 (Box 8, Folder 93)
- Chiu, S. M., 1961 December 15 (Box 8, Folder 94)
- Cleveland Museum of Art, 1939 September - 1941 June (Box 8, Folder 95)
- Cole, David C., 1962 (Box 8, Folder 96)
- Collier, Peter, 1979 February 19 (Box 8, Folder 97)
- Colloquium III, Bellagio, Italy, July 17-23, 1972, 1972 July 17-23 (Box 8, Folder 98)
- Colonial Williamsburg, Inc., 1966 (Box 8, Folder 99)
- Columbia University Oral History Research Office, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 100)
- Committee on Child Development, 1929 February (Box 8, Folder 101)
- Committee on Comparative Politics, 1971 March (Box 8, Folder 102)
- Committee on Survey of Chinese Students in American Colleges and Universities, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 103)
- Committee on the International Migration of Talent, 1970 January (Box 9, Folder 104)
- Committee on the University and World Affairs, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 105)
- Conference on Education Needs & Opportunities in the Southern States Oct. 31-Nov. 2, 1935, 1935 October 31-November 2 (Box 9, Folder 106)
- Conference on Graduate Nurse Education, 1951 April 30-May 4 (Box 9, Folder 107)
- Conference on "Industrial Arts in General Education," Shoreham Hotel, Washington, D.C., Jan. 21-23, 1937, 1937 January 21-23 (Box 9, Folder 108)
- Conference on Music in General Education, Pocono Manor Inn, Jan. 30-Feb. 1, 1936, 1936 January 30-February 1 (Box 9, Folder 109)
- Conference on the Place of Art in General Education, Briarcliff Lodge, Jan. 10-12, 1935, 1935 January 10-12 (Box 9, Folder 110)
- Cosio Villegas, Daniel, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 111)
- Co-Ct, 1917-1977; 1971-1977 (Box 9, Folder 112)
- Craig, Gordon A., 1955 October 24 (Box 9, Folder 113)
- The Impact of New Wheat Production Techniques in India and Pakistan by Ralph Cummings, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 114)
- Cu-Cz, 1970 June 21-27 (Box 9, Folder 115)
- Da-Dd, 1915-1959 (Box 10, Folder 116)
- D'Amico, Victor E., 1935 (Box 10, Folder 117)
- Darling, Samuel Taylor, 1925-1926 (Box 10, Folder 118)
- Davis, Jackson, 1936 (Box 10, Folder 119)
- De-Dh, 1964-1974 (Box 10, Folder 120)
- Destler, Chester McArthur, 1946 June (Box 10, Folder 121)
- de Souza Campos, Ernesto, 1931 March (Box 10, Folder 122)
- Dewey, John, 1929-1931 (Box 10, Folder 123)
- Di-Dn, 1932 (Box 10, Folder 124)
- Dillon, Douglas, 1971-1975 (Box 10, Folder 125)
- Do-Dt, 1943-1975; 1958-1975 (Box 10, Folder 126)
- Dollard, John, 1943 (Box 11, Folder 127)
- Downtown-Lower Manhattan Association, Inc., 1969 (Box 11, Folder 128)
- Du-Dz, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 129)
- Dugan, Alan, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 130)
- Dugas, Alvan, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 131)
- Duke University, 1946 December 31 (Box 11, Folder 132)
- Duke University, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 133)
- Ea-Ef, 1977 April 6 (Box 11, Folder 134)
- Ebenstein, William, 1960 March 15 (Box 11, Folder 135)
- Eckstein, Harry, 1961 April 10 (Box 11, Folder 136)
- Entrepreneuring, 1977 Spring (Box 11, Folder 137)
- Entrikin, J. Nicholas, 1984 October (Box 11, Folder 138)
- Epler, Stephen E., 1940 July (Box 11, Folder 139)
- Ek-Ep, 1931-1976 (Box 11, Folder 140)
- Eq-Ez, 1977-1981 (Box 11, Folder 141)
- Evans, Frank B., 1966-1971 (Box 11, Folder 142)
- Fa-Fd, 1944-1980; 1944-1946 (Box 12, Folder 143)
- FAO Seminar for Plant Breeders..., 1968 March 20 - April 2 (Box 12, Folder 144)
- Fe-Fh, 1949-1970 (Box 12, Folder 145)
- Feldman, Arnold S., 1960 March 1 (Box 12, Folder 146)
- Ferrell, John A., 1914-1954; 1914-1933 (Box 12, Folder 147)
- Fi-Fn, 1915-1949; 1938-1949 (Box 12, Folder 148)
- Fishbein, Meyer H., 1970 April (Box 12, Folder 149)
- Fisher, Donald, undated (Box 12, Folder 150)
- Flexner, Abraham, 1915 and 1927 (Box 12, Folder 151)
- Flores, Edmundo, 1963 May 20 (Box 12, Folder 152)
- Fosdick, Raymond B., 1922-1979; 1922-1931 (Box 12, Folder 153)
- The Foundation Center, 1968-1970 (Box 12, Folder 154)
- Fox, William T. R., 1952 March 25 (Box 12, Folder 155)
- Fo-Ft, 1930-1982; 1964-1982 (Box 12, Folder 156)
- Frank, Charles R., Jr., 1970 (Box 12, Folder 157)
- Franklin, William M., 1973 Januart 29 (Box 13, Folder 158)
- Freeman, G. E., 1943 (Box 13, Folder 159)
- Fu-Fz, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 160)
- Fundacao Raymundo Ottoni de Castro M., 1965 (Box 13, Folder 161)
- Furniss, Edgar S., Jr., 1954 February 5 (Box 13, Folder 162)
- Ga-Gd, 1911-1974 (Box 13, Folder 163)
- Ge-Gh, 1937 (Box 13, Folder 164)
- General Services Administration, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 165)
- Gerr, Stanley, 1944 February (Box 13, Folder 166)
- Godwin, Blake-More, 1939 (Box 13, Folder 167)
- Gondos Victor, Jr., 1947-1964 (Box 13, Folder 168)
- Goodstein, Judith R., 1984 Fall (Box 13, Folder 169)
- Gorgas, William C., 1919-1932; 1919-1924 (Box 13, Folder 170)
- Grant, James D., 1973 April 20 (Box 13, Folder 171)
- Grant, Ulysses J. & others, 1955-1963 (Box 13, Folder 172)
- Graumann, C. F., 1985 (Box 13, Folder 173)
- Gi-Gn, 1970-1971 (Box 13, Folder 174)
- Go-Gt, 1946-1980 (Box 13, Folder 175)
- Gregg, Alan (misc.), 1929-1957; 1944-1957 (Box 14, Folder 176)
- Gregg, Alan 1-34 With List, 1937-1956 (Box 14, Folder 177)
- Gregg, Alan 35-61 With List, 1921-1955 (Box 14, Folder 178)
- Gregg, Alan 62-84, 1933-1956 (Box 14, Folder 179)
- Gregg, Alan 85-94, 1931-1956 (Box 14, Folder 180)
- Gropius, Walter, 1945 (Box 14, Folder 181)
- Gruenberg, Benjamin C., 1937 (Box 14, Folder 182)
- Gu-Gz, 1924-1937 (Box 14, Folder 183)
- Ha-Hd, 1914-1977 (Box 15, Folder 184)
- Hackett, Lewis W., 1929-1960; 1929-1946 (Box 15, Folder 185)
- Hammond, H. P., 1942 February (Box 15, Folder 186)
- Hannan, J. Elizabeth, 1936 January (Box 15, Folder 187)
- Harrar, J. George, 1956-1973 (Box 15, Folder 188)
- Harrar, J. George, 1953-1972 (Box 15, Folder 189)
- Haskins, Caryl P., 1974 (Box 15, Folder 190)
- Hatheway, William H., 1957 (Box 15, Folder 191)
- Hayes, Ralph W., 1945 (Box 16, Folder 192)
- He-Hh, 1972-1980 (Box 16, Folder 193)
- Heaton, Kenneth L., 1940 (Box 16, Folder 194)
- Hegner, Robert W., 1921 (Box 16, Folder 195)
- Hemphill, Roderick J., 1961 (Box 16, Folder 196)
- Hi-Hn, 1922-1975 (Box 16, Folder 197)
- Oral History Typescript, Hirzel, William, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 198)
- Highsaw, Robert Baker, 1947-1948 (Box 16, Folder 199)
- Hoeppli, R., 1952 (Box 16, Folder 200)
- Ho-Ht, 1926-1971; 1962-1971 (Box 16, Folder 201)
- Holmes, Oliver W., 1964 January (Box 16, Folder 202)
- Howard, H. H., 1915 (Box 17, Folder 203)
- Howerton, Huey Blair, 1949-1951 (Box 17, Folder 204)
- Hunter, E. C., 1944 (Box 17, Folder 205)
- Hurd, Archer Willis, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 206)
- Hurd, Archer Willis, 1945 March (Box 17, Folder 207)
- Hurd, Archer Willis, 1946 January (Box 17, Folder 208)
- Hu-Hz, 1965-1978 (Box 17, Folder 209)
- Hydrick, John Lee, 1936 (Box 17, Folder 210)
- Institute for Advanced Study, 1954 (Box 17, Folder 211)
- Ik-Ip, 1934-1974; 1966-1974 (Box 17, Folder 212)
- Institute of Adminstrative Research, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 213)
- Institute of International Education, 1949 December (Box 18, Folder 214)
- International Conference on Intra-Uterine Conception, 2nd, New York, 1964 October 2-3 (Box 18, Folder 215)
- International Health Division, 1917-1930 (Box 18, Folder 216)
- International House, 1920-1939 (Box 18, Folder 217)
- International House of Japan, Inc., 1955-1971 (Box 18, Folder 218)
- Iowa. University. Program in Creative Writing, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 219)
- Ittelson, William H., 1954 (Box 18, Folder 220)
- Ja-Jd, 1924 (1924-1938)-1976; 1924-1938 (Box 18, Folder 221)
- Janos, Andrew C., 1964-1970 (Box 18, Folder 222)
- Je-Jh, 1968-1982 (Box 18, Folder 223)
- Jennings, Peter R., 1966-1971 (Box 18, Folder 224)
- Jo-Jt, 1957-1982 (Box 19, Folder 225)
- Jones, Merrill O., 1974 (Box 19, Folder 226)
- Joyner, Christine M., 1978 (Box 19, Folder 227)
- Junker, Buford H., 1940 (Box 19, Folder 228)
- Justice, Donald, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 229)
- Kammen, Michael, 1983 April 23 (Box 19, Folder 230)
- Kandel, I. L., 1944 (Box 19, Folder 231)
- Ka-Kd, 1940-1970 (Box 19, Folder 232)
- Kaplan, Morton A., 1959-1961 (Box 19, Folder 233)
- Katz, Evelyn, 1938 (Box 19, Folder 234)
- Kaufmann, William W., 1954 November 15 (Box 19, Folder 235)
- Kentucky. Tax Revision Commission, 1945-1946 (Box 19, Folder 236)
- Ke-Kh, 1959-1976 (Box 20, Folder 237)
- Ki-Kn, 1947-1979 (Box 20, Folder 238)
- Kissinger, Henry A., 1959 July (Box 20, Folder 239)
- Knoepfle, John, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 240)
- Knorr, Klaus E., 1956-1964 (Box 20, Folder 241)
- Knorr, Klaus E., 1954-1963 (Box 20, Folder 242)
- Knorr, Klaus E., 1956-1965 (Box 20, Folder 243)
- Ko-Kt, 1957-1965 (Box 20, Folder 244)
- Knowles, John H., 1972-1978 (Box 20, Folder 245)
- Korea, Republic of. Ministry of Health and Social Affairs, 1967 June (Box 20, Folder 246)
- Koul, Samsar Chand, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 247)
- Krampitz, Sydney D., 1978 (Box 21, Folder 248)
- Krauskopf, Robert W., 1958 October (Box 21, Folder 249)
- Kuhlman, A. F., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 250)
- Kull, Donald C., 1948 (Box 21, Folder 251)
- Kunstadter, Peter, 1965 November 30 (Box 21, Folder 252)
- Ku-Kz, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 253)
- Lancaster, John Littlepage, 1947 May (Box 21, Folder 254)
- Larsen, Christian L., 1948 June - 1949 April (Box 21, Folder 255)
- Leahy, Alice M., 1936 (Box 21, Folder 256)
- La-Ld, 1931-1968; 1931-1939 (Box 21, Folder 257)
- Le-Lh, 1945(1945-1946)-(1961-1979)1979; 1961-1979 (Box 21, Folder 258)
- Legislative Reference Bureau, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 259)
- Li-Ln, 1970-1982 (Box 22, Folder 260)
- Lo-Lt, 1923-1982 (Box 22, Folder 261)
- Lewis, John P., 1969-1971 (Box 22, Folder 262)
- Life of Christ by Chinese Artists, 1952 (Box 22, Folder 263)
- Lucie-Smith, J.D., 1921 (Box 22, Folder 264)
- Ma-Md, 1930-1974 (Box 22, Folder 265)
- McWhinney, Edward, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 266)
- Madison, James H., 1984 (Box 23, Folder 267)
- Malmgren, Harald, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 268)
- The Martha Baird Rockefeller Fund for Music, Inc., 1973 (Box 23, Folder 269)
- Martin, Roscoe C., 1942 (Box 23, Folder 270)
- Me-Mh, 1938-1984; 1970-1984 (Box 23, Folder 271)
- Mead, Pauline A., 1955 October 10 (Box 23, Folder 272)
- Melnick, Daniel, 1939-1941 (Box 23, Folder 273)
- Memorial Meeting for Simon Flexner, 1946 June 12 (Box 23, Folder 274)
- Metcalf, Keyes, 1944 (Box 23, Folder 275)
- Miles, John R., 1947 (Box 23, Folder 276)
- Mi-Mn, 1957-1979 (Box 23, Folder 277)
- Minogue, Adelaide, 1943 September (Box 23, Folder 278)
- Modelski, George, 1960-1964 (Box 23, Folder 279)
- Moholy-Nagy, Laszlo, 1946 (Box 23, Folder 280)
- Morrissey, Charles T., 1977 (Box 23, Folder 281)
- Moseman, Albert H., 1963-1970 (Box 24, Folder 282)
- Mo-Mt, 1936-1976; 1961-1976 (Box 24, Folder 283)
- Mu-Mz, 1931-1972 (Box 24, Folder 284)
- Munro, Thomas, 1940 (Box 24, Folder 285)
- Muntz, A. Philip, 1969 (Box 24, Folder 286)
- Myers, Will M., 1968-1971 (Box 24, Folder 287)
- Myren, Delbert T., 1969-1971 (Box 24, Folder 288)
- National Center for Productivity and Quality of Working Life, 1975-1976 (Box 24, Folder 289)
- National Commission on Productivity and Work Quality, 1975 October (Box 24, Folder 290)
- Na-Nd, 1962-1968 (Box 24, Folder 292)
- National Academy of Sciences, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 293)
- National Archives Bulletins, 1944 June (Box 25, Folder 294)
- National Archives Staff Information Circulars, 1950 May - July (Box 25, Folder 295)
- National Archives Staff Information Papers, 1950-1971 (Box 25, Folder 296)
- National Bureau of Economic Research, 1947-1963 (Box 25, Folder 297)
- Ne-Nh, 1951-1979 (Box 25, Folder 298)
- Nelson, James R., 1953 March 9 (Box 25, Folder 299)
- New York State Atomic and Space Development Authority, 1970-1972 (Box 25, Folder 300)
- New York. State Education Department. Office of State History., 1972 January (Box 25, Folder 301)
- New York State Historical Association, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 302)
- New York Times. Oral History Program., 1975 (Box 25, Folder 303)
- Ni-Nn, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 304)
- No-Nt, 1921-1932 (Box 26, Folder 305)
- Noguchi, Hideyo, 1920-1931 (Box 26, Folder 306)
- Noguchi, Hideyo; Reprints, 1919-1925 (Box 26, Folder 307)
- North Carolina Board of Higher Education, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 308)
- North Carolina State University, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 309)
- Norton, John K., 1946 (Box 26, Folder 310)
- Nu-Nz, 1975-1977 (Box 26, Folder 311)
- Oa-Of, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 312)
- Official Guidebook of Colonial Williamsburg, 1951 (Box 26, Folder 313)
- Oficina de Estudios Especiales, 1954 (Box 27, Folder 314)
- Ok-Op, 1961 March (Box 27, Folder 315)
- Orozco, J. C., 1934 (Box 27, Folder 316)
- Owens, Patrick N., 1966 November (Box 27, Folder 317)
- Owens, William A., 1960 (Box 27, Folder 318)
- Pa-Pd, 1915-(1961-1974)-1988; 1961-1974 (Box 27, Folder 319)
- Paarlberg, Don, 1970 December (Box 27, Folder 320)
- Pan American Festival, Annual, 1963 April 8-11 (Box 27, Folder 321)
- Paret, Peter, 1961 June 1 (Box 27, Folder 322)
- Parker District High School Faculty, 1942 (Box 27, Folder 323)
- Patino-Camargo, Luis, 1973 July 12 (Box 27, Folder 324)
- Pearce, Richar M., Jr., 1919-1931 (Box 27, Folder 325)
- Pe-Ph, 1951-1973 (Box 27, Folder 326)
- Peiping. Palace Museum., 1931 (Box 27, Folder 327)
- Peking Union Medical College, 1917-1940 (Box 27, Folder 328)
- Penington, Alan H., 1984 September (Box 27, Folder 329)
- Pi-Pn, 1968-1977 (Box 27, Folder 330)
- Pokorny & Pertz, Architects and Planners, 1970-1973 (Box 28, Folder 331)
- Population Council, undated (Box 28, Folder 332)
- Posner, Ernst, 1940 (Box 28, Folder 333)
- Progressive Education Assn, 1941 (Box 28, Folder 334)
- Po-Pt, 1968-1973 (Box 28, Folder 335)
- Pu-Pz, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 336)
- Puerto Rico Department of Health, 1959 (Box 28, Folder 337)
- Ra-Rd, 1963-1972 (Box 28, Folder 338)
- Rachou, Rene G., 1965 January (Box 28, Folder 339)
- Ramos, Maximo, 1961 (Box 29, Folder 340)
- Rankin, Robert S., 1946 (Box 29, Folder 341)
- Rannells, Edward Warder, 1946 June (Box 29, Folder 342)
- Re-Rh, 1963-1973 (Box 29, Folder 343)
- Read, Thornton, 1960-1964 (Box 29, Folder 344)
- Reyes, Arturo C., 1954 May (Box 29, Folder 345)
- Richards, I. A., 1937 March (Box 29, Folder 346)
- Ri-Rn, 1932-1970 (Box 29, Folder 347)
- Robertson, Jerry, 1955 (Box 30, Folder 348)
- Ro-Rt, 1925-1976 (Box 30, Folder 349)
- Rockefeller Archive Center, 1974-1980 (Box 30, Folder 350)
- Rockefeller Brothers Fund, 1965 (Box 30, Folder 351)
- Rockefeller Foundation, 1930-1979 (Box 30, Folder 352)
- Rockefeller Foundation, 1915-1974 (Box 30, Folder 353)
- Rockefeller Foundation. Agricultural Sciences Division. Chilean Agricultural Program., 1955-1956 (Box 31, Folder 354)
- Rockefeller Foundation, 1922 October (Box 31, Folder 355)
- Rockefeller Foundation, 1950-1979 (Box 31, Folder 356)
- Rockefeller Foundation Staff Newsletter, 1966-1972 (Box 31, Folder 357)
- Rockefeller Foundation Trustee Newsletter, 1975 February - August (Box 31, Folder 358)
- Rockefeller, John D., 1897-1976 (Box 31, Folder 359)
- Rockefeller, John D., Jr., 1915(1915-1937)-1960; 1915-1937 (Box 32, Folder 360)
- Rockefeller, John Davison, 3rd, 1968-1978 (Box 32, Folder 361)
- Rockefeller, Laurance Spelman, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 362)
- Rockefeller, Nelson A., 1976-1979 (Box 32, Folder 363)
- Rockefeller University, 1940-1976 (Box 32, Folder 364)
- Rockefeller University, 1968-1976 (Box 33, Folder 365)
- Rockefeller University, 1976-1978 (Box 33, Folder 366)
- Rockefeller University. Caspary Gallery., 1976 (Box 33, Folder 367)
- Romulo, Carlos P., 1965 (Box 33, Folder 368)
- Rose, Wickliffe, 1911-1932 (Box 33, Folder 369)
- Rosenau, James N., 1963-1967 (Box 33, Folder 370)
- Rosicky, B., 1960 January (Box 33, Folder 371)
- Royal Institute of International Affairs, 1946 (Box 34, Folder 372)
- Russell, Paul F., 1931-1957 (Box 34, Folder 373)
- Ru-Rz, 1960 (Box 34, Folder 374)
- Rustow, Dankwart A., 1956 March 1 (Box 34, Folder 375)
- Ruttan, Vernon W., 1965-1968 (Box 34, Folder 376)
- Sa-Sd, 1923-1975; 1923-1937 (Box 34, Folder 377)
- Savell, Isabelle K., 1962 (Box 34, Folder 378)
- Scalapino, Robert A., 1961 February (Box 34, Folder 379)
- Schellenberg, T. R., 1939-1956 (Box 34, Folder 380)
- School Health Study Committee, 1938 May 1 (Box 35, Folder 381)
- Se-Sh, 1922(1959-1975)-1975; 1959-1975 (Box 35, Folder 382)
- Seabury, Paul, 1957 June 26 (Box 35, Folder 383)
- Seal, Incorporated, undated (Box 35, Folder 384)
- Shaw, Gerald W., 1946 October (Box 35, Folder 385)
- Si-Sn, 1939-1977 (Box 35, Folder 386)
- Silliman, Benjamin, Jr., 1949 (Box 35, Folder 387)
- So-St, 1928-1976 (Box 35, Folder 388)
- Southwest Regional Land Tenure Project, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 389)
- Snyder, Glenn H., 1959 January 2 (Box 36, Folder 390)
- Spence, L., 1957-1967 (Box 36, Folder 391)
- Sprout, Harold, 1968 March (Box 36, Folder 392)
- Stage, Harry H., 1944 February (Box 36, Folder 393)
- Stakman, E. C., 1946-1969 (Box 36, Folder 394)
- Steiner, Zara S., 1961 March 20 (Box 36, Folder 395)
- Stewart, R. B., 1941 August (Box 36, Folder 396)
- Stewart, R. M., 1948 October 19 (Box 36, Folder 397)
- Story, Isabelle F., 1957 (Box 36, Folder 398)
- Su-Sz, 1937-1938 (Box 36, Folder 399)
- Ta-Td, 1958-1966 (Box 36, Folder 400)
- Tanaka, Akira, 1964-1970 (Box 36, Folder 401)
- Te-Th, 1952-1982 (Box 36, Folder 402)
- Thompson, Kenneth, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 403)
- Ti-Tn, 1970-1971 (Box 37, Folder 404)
- To-Tz, 1956-1973 (Box 37, Folder 405)
- Trever, Karl L., 1941 July (Box 37, Folder 406)
- Tucker, Robert C., 1963 September 15 (Box 37, Folder 407)
- Ua-Uz, 1973-1975 (Box 37, Folder 408)
- Union Church of Pocantico Hills, 1965-1981 (Box 37, Folder 409)
- U.S. Congress, 82d, 2d Session. House. Select Committee to Investigate Foundations & Other Organizations, 1953 (Box 37, Folder 410)